Teresa Lee | teresalee1231@gmail.com | 206-466-9755

BACKGROUND

Recent university graduate with 4 years of experience coding in Java, Python, and C++. Experienced in working in a fast paced setting. Looking for front end, back end, or full stack development roles. Has a willingness to grow and improve.

EDUCATION

B.S. Computer Science

University of Washington - Seattle, WA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer | Fred Hutchinson Research Center - Seattle WA | 06/2021 - 09/2021

- Developed an R package that finds the correlation between survivability and different microbiome bacteria.
- Parsed through classified patient data to find relevant data for the model.
- Implemented features that show the correlation with graphs with the specific model being inputted,
- Used Git version control and GitHub to share and review code.
- Participated in weekly meetings providing valuable insight to the project.
- Worked remotely in a 13 week period.

PROJECTS

Personal Website | https://teresalee1231.github.io/ | 03/2024 - TBD

- Developed a personal website using React.
- Experimented with different design choices to fit my personal aesthetic.

Slimes 'n' Boxes | CSE 481d Games Capstone | 01/2023 - 03/2023

- Developed a game from scratch within 10 weeks using GDScript in the Godot game engine.
- Lead designer within a team of 5 people.
- Posted on social media and advertised the game.
- Presented our game in a gaming convention setting.
- Went through the process of the game development cycle in 10 weeks.

Final Project | CSE 442 Data Visualization | 11/2022 - 12/2022

- Used d3, is to create interactive visualizations from Pokemon data.
- Helped design the website that these visualizations are showcased in.
- Integrated the techniques and tools about data visualization I have learned in class.

Cat Vs Dog Classification Kaggle Competition | CSE 455 Final Project | 02/2022 - 03/2022

- Trained on pre-existing image classification models to produce a convolutional neural network to classify images in a Kaggle Competition dataset.
- Assisted with the implementation of the model using PyTorch.
- Trained model from scratch using DarkNet.
- Trained model using transfer learning using ResNet18 and ResNet 18 SWSL.

OTHER EXPERIENCES

TRIO Student Associate | UW OMA&D TRIO SSS - Seattle WA | 02/2022 - 06/2022

- Designed flyers and posters for UW OMA&D TRIO SSS using Canva.
- Posted on social media to promote these events.
- Updated the TRIO website (Wordpress).

Fundraising Chair | Phi Sigma Rho Sorority - Mu Chapter | 03/24/2021 - 06/03/2022

- Raised over \$700 for the Leukemia and Lymphoma Society.
- Organized and led fundraising events.
- Worked alongside the sorority's VP of finance and Panhellenic's VP of finance.
- Designed flyers and posted using Canva.
- Demonstrated leadership skills by working with a small group and discussing ideas.